the ICICI Bank company stop started with
the counterpoint in the green with a
profit of zero point twenty percent I'd
rupees 380 on the NSE despite the market
rally over 0.76 percent the global
broker Jefferies maintain the by call on
the country's largest second private
sector London ICICI Bank its valuation
are attractive at current level and it
is among our optics in sector it added
the monetization of games on stake in
subsidiary held the bank mobilised
rupees 3090 corrode ICICI Bank sold
three point 96 percent stake in ICICI
Lombard general insurance company for
rupees 2,450 corrode on June 19 and 1.5
percent state shareholding in ICICI
Prudential Life Insurance Company for
rupees 840 Goren on June 22nd through
open market transactions Jeffrey C it
has raised its target price on this top
two rupees 460 per share from the army a
target of rupees 450 implying 25 percent
upside potential from current level as
the bank offers a favorable risk reward
with the reselling asset quality risk
and finally to avoid huge losses in the
stock market leaving sharra strict
stop-loss and thanks for out of
confidence